I should just skip! Pretend to be sick or something like that…
Bon, je sèche les cours aujourd'hui. Je vais dire que je suis malade !
Ouch… My elbow…
Aie, mon coude !
Are you alright?
Tu vas bien ?
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
Désolé, je ne regardais pas devant moi.
I-It's my fault for not looking where I was going…  Sorry.
C-C'est aussi ma faute… Désolé.
Thank you…
Merci…
By the way, is this yours?
C'est à toi ?
It seems like it's pretty important to you, huh?
Ça a l'air important.
Since I've already finished with the inspection and all, how about I hold onto it for you?
J'ai déjà passé l'inspection, je vais le garder sur moi pour toi.
B-But…
M-Mais…
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Tu fais quoi ? Allez !
Ah! Right! Sorry!
Ah, désolé !
I'll wait inside for you at lunch.
On se voit à midi.
Clothes, check. Belongings, check. No issues.
Vêtements et matériel. Rien à signaler.
It's been a while, Loneal Gravis.
Ça faisait longtemps, Lonile.
Hm? Ah, yes…
Hm ? Ah, oui…
Make sure to come by the council room after school.
Vies impérativement me voir dans la salle du conseil des élèves après les cours !
Huh? Why?
Hein ? Pourquoi ?
Don't tell me that you've forgotten about the contract!?
Tu as oublié les termes du contrat !?
Loneal, sorry for the wait.
Désolé de t'avoir fait attendre.
Oh, it's you…!
Oh, c'est toi !
I'm Zeno Orwen, a second-year.
Zeno Orwen. Je suis endeuxième année,
You can call me Zeno.
tu peux m'appeler Zeno.
Here's your pouch.
Tiens.
T-Thank you very much.
M-Merci beaucoup.
How do you know my name, though?
Comment tu sais comment je m'appele ?
You're pretty famous for being a talented potions maker.
T'es connu pour tes talents en concotion magiques.
But there are also the rumors about how you've become quite close to the royal family lately.
Et plus récemment, il y a beaucoup de rumeurs à propos de toi et du prince.
Do I really stand out that much when I'm with Alec?!
Ma relation avec Alek est si visible !?
It made me curious, so I wanted to talk to you.
J'étais curieux, donc je voulais essayer de te parler.
Alright, I'm leaving.
Bon je te laisse !
Wait, is there anything I can do to thank you?
Attends ! Est-ce que je peux faire quelque chose pour te remercier ?
Hmm… Oh, yeah!
Hm…
I heard about this interesting notebook your club has…
J'ai entendu parler d'un livret intéressant dans ton club.
It's Alec!
Alek !
He's just as handsome as ever!
Il est si beau !
Loneal.
Lonile.
Would it be alright if I talked to you for a bit?
Ah ! Puis-je avoir un moment ?
Sure.
Bien sûr.
Who are you?
T'es qui toi ?
What a pleasure to meet you, Your Highness.
Enchanté.
I'm Zeno Orwen, a second-year student.
Je m'appelle Zeno Orwen. Je suis en deuxième année.
Orwen… Isn't your father a count who runs his own business?
Orwen… Le comté qui s'occupe de la chambre de commerce ?
Indeed.
C'est ça.
And I'm also Loneal's friend!
Je suis aussi l'ami de Lonile.
He considers me a friend?
Il me considère comme son ami ?
So, I hope from now on you'll allow us ample time to spend together as friends.
Si vous pouviez laisser un peu de temps à Lonile pour qu'il puisse s'amuse avec moi, j'en serais ravi.
I'll consider it.
J'y penserai.
Huh? What's going on?
Hein ? C'est quoi cette tension ?
Loneal, let's go.
Viens, Lonile.
O-Okay…
O-Ok…
Sorry! See you later, Zeno.
Au revoir !
I see.
Je vois.
Alec… Are you angry? Did I do-—
Est-ce que vous êtes en colère… ? Est-ce que j'ai…
Your highness… What…?
Prince…
Loneal…
Lonile…
Seeing you with your friend seems to have made me jealous.
Rien que de te voir avec un ami me rend jaloux…
He's just a friend… My first one at that!
C'est juste un ami… C'est le premier que j'ai…
My favorite character's… jealous over me?
Il est jaloux… ?
I…
Je…
I won't let anyone else be your number one. Not even a friend.
Ne peut tolérer que quelqu'un d'autre soit ton premier, peu importe la catégorie.
Not there…
Pas là…
Don't be so rough…!
Tu me titilles trop…
You're too attractive, I can't control myself.
Tu est juste trop mignon, je ne peux pas résister.
I want to cum… But I shouldn't…
Je veux jouir… Mais je ne dois pas…
Loneal.
Lonile.
I hope that one day, you too, will feel the same.
Un jour, j'espère que toi aussi, tu seras jaloux.
I already… feel that way..
Je le suis déjà…
But if I were to act on such feelings of jealousy…
Mais si je le dis…
Recently, there have been times when you won't show me your face…
Tu as cette habitude de cacher ton visage…
To think you've been hiding such an expression of pure bliss…
C'est parce que ton expression est coquine ?
No…
Non…
You're so cute.
Tu es mignon.
My Loneal.
Mon Lonile.
I want to be inside you.
Je veux être en toi…
I want to be consumed by your supple pink flesh as it takes me in whole…
Je veux m'enfoncer dans ton petit coin rose…
While teasing your nipples with each thrust…
Et titiller tes tétons dans la cadence…
Until I pour my love inside of you..
Puis finir par verser mon amour en toi…
From dawn to dusk… All day long…
Du matin au soir… Toute la journée…
Loneal… Thank you.
Lonile… Merci.
I feel better thanks to you.
Je me sens mieux grâce à toi.
I think it's best… if I just stopped thinking for today…
J'ai plus envie de penser à quoi que ce soit…
You came, Loneal Gravis.
Lonile. Te voilà.
Yes.
Oui.
No one besides you ever participates in the Magic Compound Club.
Tu es le seul membre actif de ton club.
You can hardly call this a club.
C'est difficile de justifier son existence dans ces conditions.
However…
Cependant.
We've been allowing the club's existence under the condition
Nous avons fait une exception en échange du fait tu produises
that you provide the school with potions.
des potions pour l'école.
Huh?
Hein ?
But you haven't delivered any potions lately!
Mais ça fait un moment que tu n'as rien produit !
I heard that you got hurt, so I extended the deadline..
J'ai entendu que tu avais eu un problème de santé, donc j'ai étenu la date limite…
But you have only three days left!
Mais ça suffit ! Il te reste trois jours !
If you fail to deliver the potions by then, the club will be terminated!
Si tu ne produis pas de potions d'ici là, c'est la fin de ton club !
What?!
Hein ?!